Benjamin Franklin Papers Part 7 -- Letters to Franklin 1783 January-November Mss.B.F85inventory07
American Philosophical Society
- Letters to Benjamin Franklin.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 November 28; 1p.; Chaumont, Jacques-Donatien Leray de, 1725-1803
    A bill for candles.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 November 29; A.L.S. 2p.; Le Roy, Jean Baptiste
    Begging Franklin to grant an interview to M. du Trône, a young physician for whom he has already written two letters of recommendation to friends in Philadelphia.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 November 29; L. in 3d P. 2p.; Grand, Ferdinand
    Sending a copy of a decree of Council concerning the cash discount; explaining the rights this gives the shareholders.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 November 30; A.L.S. 3p.; Kéralio, Agathon Guynement, chevalier de
    Introducing M. de Gourdon, who has served with him in the Military School and is the kind of Frenchman Franklin likes. His reasons for thinking there will be no war in the East; quotes from a St. Petersburg letter, showing that in case Prince Potemkin should die of his illness, the Empress would decide for peace.